<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journal on Bo Shao</title>
    <link>//localhost:3843/categories/journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journal on Bo Shao</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:3843/categories/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring DeepAR</title>
      <link>//localhost:3843/post/2024/11/17/exploring-deepar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:3843/post/2024/11/17/exploring-deepar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;November 17, 2024&lt;/strong&gt; – Today, I want to share some insights into one of the most exciting areas of my recent research: the DeepAR model with attention mechanisms. DeepAR is a state-of-the-art probabilistic forecasting model that has transformed how we approach time series forecasting problems, especially in high-dimensional and dynamic environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my research, I’ve been applying DeepAR to optimize demand forecasting and decision-making in supply chains. By incorporating an &lt;strong&gt;attention mechanism&lt;/strong&gt;, the model not only captures temporal patterns but also assigns weights to important features, enabling it to focus on the most relevant demand drivers. This improvement significantly enhances its forecasting accuracy compared to traditional methods.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First International Conference Presentation at OMEA/MBAA 2024</title>
      <link>//localhost:3843/post/2024/04/10/first-international-conference-presentation-at-omea/mbaa-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:3843/post/2024/04/10/first-international-conference-presentation-at-omea/mbaa-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April 10, 2024&lt;/strong&gt; – Today, I had the incredible experience of presenting at the OMEA/MBAA 2024 conference in Chicago. This was my first time speaking at an international conference, and I was really nervous. Despite the nerves, I learned a lot and gained valuable insights from this opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Presenting in front of an international audience was challenging but rewarding. I realize there’s still much room for improvement, and I need to keep pushing myself to grow and gain confidence in these settings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embarking on a New Journey</title>
      <link>//localhost:3843/post/2023/08/07/embarking-on-a-new-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:3843/post/2023/08/07/embarking-on-a-new-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;August 7, 2023&lt;/strong&gt; – Today, I set off for the United States, bidding farewell to my parents, friends, and everything familiar to embark on a new journey.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This day is filled with a mix of emotions – a bittersweet moment of saying goodbye while feeling excited for what lies ahead. As I looked back at the faces of my loved ones, I felt both the warmth of their support and the weight of leaving them behind. Heading to the U.S. is not just a trip; it’s a step toward growth, exploration, and new experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
